(soft ambient music)
(wind whooshing)
(ominous orchestral music)
(voice whispering indistinctly)
(gentle rock music)
(car whooshing)
(gentle rock music continues)
- [Kai] I think this trip
might be what you need, babe.
The semester's over.
It's time to celebrate.
- [Mia] What sort of vacation
home is this place again?
- [Kai] (chuckling)
Honestly, don't know much
about it other than
it's a free trip
and Angel and his
girl invited us.
- Angel girl?
What bimbo is it this week?
- [Kai] Be nice, babe.
She's actually not as
bad as some of the other.
(phone ringing)
(phone clicking)
And I know it's not
Paris or a Milan.
I just thought after
the year you had
that some quiet time
away would be nice.
- [Mia] Thank you.
You're right.
A change in scenery
is what I need.
(crickets chirping)
(car whooshing)
How can you see
anything in this fog?
- Can you turn on my defrost?
- Slow down a bit.
I can't see.
- I got this, baby.
- Kai!
(tires screeching)
- Why did you scream?
- You didn't see that thing
in the middle of the road?
- No.
- It was in the
middle of the road.
You just hit it.
- Hit what?
What did it look like?
Dude, you just screamed
to save something's life.
What was it?
- [Mia] I don't know.
- (sighing) A squirrel?
A possum?
Deer?
- It looked big and green.
- Big and green?
Babe, no animal
looks big and green.
- [Mia] I dunno.
Oh God.
- Do you think your medicine is
causing you to see things?
- What?
- You know, all those
pharmaceutical drug
commercials always have like
a whole minute where
they list off all the,
the, the side effects.
I don't know.
Maybe hallucinating
is one of them.
- This is real.
I know what I saw.
- It's okay.
I believe you.
(Kai sighing)
(engine revving)
- What?
What?
- I think we have a flat.
- Oh God.
How far are we?
- About 20 minutes out, I think.
Luckily I know how
to change a tire.
- (scoffing) You know
how to change a tire.
That kind of turns me on.
- Oh yeah? (exclaiming)
(Mia laughing)
- I'll be right back.
No, stay in.
I got it.
- It's dark out.
The least I could do
is hold a flashlight.
(door clicking)
(ratchet clicking)
(brush rustling)
- [Kai] Babe, I need some light.
- Sorry.
- I'm talented, but
I'm not a magician.
- [Mia] Sorry.
- You can leave the,
the flashlight here
and get back in the
car if you want.
- I'm, I'm good.
I'm good.
How much longer?
- That's it.
(sighing) I don't think
this donut spare is gonna
get us back on Monday though.
I'm gonna have to call AAA.
(brush rustling)
(crickets chirping)
- Oh my god.
- Hey.
No, babe.
No.
- Oh.
- Damn it.
- Oh, I'm sorry.
- The, the front
camera's broken.
No, no face ID and I
can't use the screen.
So how am I supposed
to unlock this?
- You can unlock your phone
using your watch, right?
- There's my little genius.
- Hey, Siri, call AAA.
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(twig snapping)
(brush rustling)
(ominous music)
(Mia gasping)
Babe, come on.
Let's go.
AAA is gonna be at the
house in the morning.
(door clicking)
AAA's gonna be here in the
morning with a new tire.
- [Mia] I'm sorry about today.
(sighing) Let's go have fun.
- Angel's Dad let him drive
the car this weekend and-
- [Mia] Oh God.
He's gonna be insufferable.
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(people shouting indistinctly)
(footsteps thudding)
- They're here. (screaming)
I am all sticky.
- Oh God.
(upbeat electronic music)
(upbeat electronic
music continues)
- Hey, Mia.
Good to see you.
You're here just in time.
The hot tub is ready to go.
- Great.
What's her name again?
- Vicki.
- I think this is the one.
- Hey, V fam, we
are streaming live
from Lake Pearl.
Huge shout out to Antoninias
for these super hot swimsuits.
- Oh, don't tell me
she's one of those.
- 20% discount.
- She makes more than me
and you combined with those
millions of followers.
- Not everything's about money.
- Mia.
Of course you feel that way
with that (laughing)
mythological studies degree.
- Ah.
- You're wasting your
money on an education
that you can get for
free on Wikipedia.
- That's enough.
- Yeah.
- We'll be in soon.
- I'll be up early.
- Mm-hmm.
Fuck.
(Kai sighing)
(door clicking)
(doors clicking)
(ominous music)
(intense music)
- [Mia] Mom!
(Kai sighing)
- I'm sorry.
I, I didn't know it
was a lake house.
We can go if you want.
Oh shit.
The tire.
We can go first
thing in the morning.
- It's okay.
- No, it's not.
Let's go.
- I can't be scared
of water forever.
- (sighing) Well, we, we
won't get on any boats.
We'll just, we'll
stay away from it.
Okay?
- It's fine.
It's been here.
I can do this.
(Vicki shouting indistinctly)
- [Kai] He's in love apparently.
- He's horny.
- Same thing.
Come here.
- Babe, not here.
Not here. (laughing)
- Don't be shy, guys.
Show us what five years
in love looks like.
- [Angel] That's what's up, Kai.
Show us honeymooners how
to keep that fire burning.
(all laughing)
(upbeat rock music)
- Oh no, no.
Kai, no, no suitcase on the bed.
- I need you to loosen up
just a little bit, babe.
- You just dragged
that through the dirt
and put all that on the bed.
- Okay.
That's fair.
(box clicking)
- Good evening.
- Oh.
Who are you?
- Greetings.
Welcome to Lake Pearl.
It's truly my pleasure to
host you and my family's home.
My name's Sabrina.
- Kai Oats.
- Mia Daughtry.
- Welcome to Lake Pearl.
What brings you here?
- Couldn't pass
up on a free trip.
YOLO.
(Mia laughing)
- I'm sorry, what is YOLO?
- It's a saying.
You only live once.
- I see.
We would say live for today,
for tomorrow may never come.
- Ah.
- Same sentiment.
- Exactly.
Um, I guess we just wanted some
peace and quiet this summer.
Place seems pretty secluded.
- Good fences make
the best neighbors.
- Do you have wifi?
I don't have service anywhere.
- Our wifi will be
down for tonight.
Tech guys can't come
till tomorrow to fix it.
However, we do have a
landline in the kitchen.
- Might be good to
disconnect for a day or two.
- Yeah, you're probably right.
- God is often found in
seclusion and solitude.
- Right.
- Well, if you need
anything, I'll be downstairs.
- Oh, you're staying
in the same house?
- Oh, you won't know I'm here.
I promise.
- (laughing) I
hate these Airbnbs.
- This is not an Airbnb.
- And what Backpage
of the internet did
you find this place?
- Actually, my family
and I used to spend
every summer here.
Sabrina hasn't aged one bit.
Like how is she still
this fine? (laughing)
Wait until I tell my
brother about this.
- So you guys used to
spend every summer here?
- We'll come every few years,
from when I was
five until about 15.
- [Mia] Why'd you stop?
- I'm not sure.
I vaguely remember
some sketchy shit
in the news about this area.
Or maybe my parents
just got tired
of spending every
summer in the same lake.
Who knows?
I'm sorry.
I know family is touchy for you.
- Oh no.
You should be able
to talk about your
childhood and parents.
- And it's okay for
you to still grieve.
There's no, there's no timeline
for that kind of stuff.
I just want to create
new memories with you,
see you smile again.
That was pretty good.
That was good.
- So it is an Airbnb.
- Potato, potato.
Hurry up and unpack.
(Mia laughing)
- No.
(soft rock music)
(soft rock music continues)
(notification popping)
(electricity crackling)
(footsteps thudding)
(brush rustling)
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
(phone thudding)
(trunk clicking)
(Vicki sighing)
(Vicki grunting)
(footsteps thudding)
- Here you go.
- Shit.
Oh, where the hell
did you come from?
- Around.
I'm always around.
- And who the hell are you?
- Call me Mr. Leonard.
I'm the groundskeeper
on this property.
Okay.
You need help with your bag?
- No, I'm good.
- You sure are a pretty thing.
By the way, no, sir.
- [Vicki] Excuse me.
- Where I come from,
we show our elders a
little bit of deference.
Yes sir, no sir, the whatnot.
- Well, you see where I'm from,
we keep the sirs and
ma'ams, you know,
for the person
cutting the check.
- Yeah, that so?
That's plain
unfortunate for you.
- Well, (laughing) goodnight.
- Yeah, you too.
Good night.
Ain't no bed bugs biting that.
That's a shame.
(ominous music)
I pay my respect
and I wasn't writing
you any check.
Yeah, well,
gonna be writing you a check
here pretty soon, little girl.
Let's see how you and this
slutty outfit like that.
Let me help you with your bag.
Mmmm.
Yeah, fuck her.
(Mr. Leonard grunting)
(door creaking)
(flashlight clicking)
(door slamming)
(ominous music)
(Vicki breathing heavily)
(Vicki grunting and coughing)
Oh God.
(wall banging)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(bottle cap clacking)
(water dripping)
(ominous music)
- Scared?
(Vicki gasping)
(Vicki laughing)
(ominous music continues)
Oh fuck yeah.
What?
Well, what are you doing?
No, don't.
- You sprayed me earlier.
Use your hands.
(vibrator whirring)
(Vicki moaning)
Oh God.
Fuck.
(Vicki moaning)
(Angel grunting)
(Angel whimpering)
(Vicki laughing)
♪ I put my hand upon your ♪
♪ Hand upon your hip ♪
♪ I put my hand upon your hip ♪
♪ When I dip, you dip, we dip ♪
♪ I put my ♪
(Vicki exhaling)
- How can I cook with her
crotch on the counter?
(Vicki exhaling)
- Ah.
It looks like the king
and queen finally decided
to join the party.
- I'm not much of a partier.
- Obviously.
- How is the hot tub?
Hot?
- Very hot.
- Well, I'm starving,
so what are we gonna
eat for dinner?
- We could do fish and chips.
- Ooh, I love night fishing.
- This lake is not
known for fishing.
As many times as I've come here,
I have yet to see one fish.
- You don't seem like
the fishing type anyways.
- Yeah, babe, maybe they
were just hiding from you.
- Whatever.
It's a known fact
that, that there's
no fish in that lake.
Now that I think about it,
I rarely saw any
wildlife out there.
It was always very quiet.
- Seen any green animals?
(Angel laughing)
Listen RL Stine, there's
no Frankenstein out.
There might be a goon.
- Well, way way
way back in my day,
this place was bustling
with fish, bears,
birds, and every possible
creature you can imagine.
- Well, what happened?
- Man.
Humans doing like humans do.
- Death and destruction.
- Bingo.
- But nature always
gets her revenge.
- She sure does.
Well, I didn't
mean to intterrupt,
but I just wanted to
make sure you're all good
before I retire to my
quarters for the night.
- Your place is amazing.
- Yeah.
It's very vintage and shique.
You know, I can help get the
word out about this place.
My followers always love
to know what I'm up to.
- Who's your service provider?
I don't have any
signal anywhere.
- I don't have a signal either.
I just record for the recap.
I wait to post my location
till after I leave.
You can never be too safe.
Besides one tag for me on Monday
and your whole season
will be sold out.
- Trust me, she's legit.
- Well, you're too kind,
but I think I'd rather the
springs remain a hidden gem.
- She's gold.
- Back to business.
What the fuck are we gonna
eat if we can't fish?
- Well, I brought some
packs of fish with us.
We can go out back and
cook 'em over a fire.
- Rugged.
I likee, I likee.
But first let's
have a little fun.
- Oh.
- That is why I love this girl.
- Yes.
- Always thinking ahead.
- Shrooms.
I haven't done those
since summer 2019.
- Little microdose for the
hell of it? (chuckling)
- Ah, I think I'll,
I'll keep it in 2019.
- Pussy.
- Shut the fuck up.
- Hey babe, why'd you invite
this square ass couple?
- Excuse me.
- Look, it's gonna be
a long ass weekend.
At least we're
gonna have some fun.
(upbeat music)
(water gurgling)
- Fuck it.
Give it to me.
- [Kai] Babe, no.
(upbeat music continues)
- Here's to a happy trip.
- Let's get out of here.
(upbeat music continues)
- You sure this is a good idea?
- You said we were here
to have fun, right?
- I mean how is this gonna
mix with your prescriptions?
- I guess we'll find out.
(upbeat music continues)
(Mia laughing)
- Hmm.
All right.
Who's got it?
- Got what?
- The scary fireside story.
This is the prime location
and ambiance for one.
- I know some, real
creepy, tragic ones.
- What you kids doing?
(ominous music)
Doing some kind of
campfire bullshit?
- Guys, this is Mr. Leonard.
(can thudding)
- I am acquainted
with your girlfriend,
and seeing that I'm
a tad under-dressed
or over-dressed for this party.
Y'all about to tell
ghost stories, right?
- Yeah.
- Yes, sir.
Yes we were.
- Mmm.
Yeah.
More like it'll be some
lame story about a man
with a hook for a hand, right?
Some stupid story about some
animal eat sheep or whatnot.
You look like you've had
an alien go to town on you
more than one time.
(all laughing)
There's only one story
really worth telling here,
and Andre know it.
It is a true story.
It ain't no bull story.
- I can't mess that
one up, Mr. Leonard.
I know that one like
the back of my hand.
- Back of your hand.
Couple hundred years
ago had these folks
live right here on
the edge of this lake.
They had a water
god. (indistinct)
That guy in Egypt what said
that thing about
water that one time.
- I am water.
- I read that somewhere.
Anyway, these is
really angry folks
what live up on a hill,
took into their heads
one day they wanted
the land down here for themself.
He come charging
down out the hill,
stoning or swording
everybody in their prime.
Wonder folk, they
kind of peaceful,
they outnumbered our clan
and far back best they could.
Last hundred or 150 men,
they wound up down
there with their backs
to the water, wondering
why their water goddess
ain't coming to save 'em.
Finally decided
what's the best way
to get the attention of a God.
They all walked into
that one on their own.
Round themselves.
Every single one of them.
Meaning not every
single one of them.
She come up out the
water all right.
If you played some hell
with those hill people.
Trouble is you drag something
like that up outta hell,
it's kind of hard to control.
And once in a while
they get a taste again.
You know?
Night like this.
It all wet and black.
That little breeze
coming in on the lake.
I know you feel it.
Maybe she come
outta here tonight.
She bite into one of y'all.
Sucked the soul right out you.
It won't even take a long time
and know you to live through it.
They only gonna wish they died.
You have a nice evening.
Don't be making stains
on the cushions.
I just Scotchgarded them.
- [Angel] Take
care, Mr. Leonard.
- [Mr. Leonard] You too, Andre.
- My name's Angel.
- Scared the shit out of me.
- Who's it gonna be?
Who's gonna be the
sacrificial lamb?
- Oh God,
- I'll do it.
Me.
- It took forever.
Like, damn.
He was the scary story.
Jesus Christ.
You know him?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
Babe, are you okay?
(upbeat dance music)
(upbeat dance music continues)
(Vicki laughing)
(all laughing)
(upbeat dance music continues)
(Mia screaming)
Hey, hey.
Hey, it's all mental,
it's all mental.
Hey, take a deep breath.
Deep breath.
(Mia breathing heavily)
It's okay, it's okay.
No.
(ominous music)
(Mia screaming)
What, what?
Hey, what, what, what?
What, hey.
It's okay.
Hey, hey, sit down.
(Mia breathing heavily)
(Mia whimpering)
- Hey, bro.
We're going for a
swim in the lake.
Coming with?
- [Kai] No, I'm
gonna chill here.
Make sure she's okay.
- Well, the nights
that I can't remember
usually hold the best memories.
(Mia breathing heavily)
(upbeat dance music continues)
(crickets chirping)
(Vicki gasping)
- Something just
touched my foot.
- It was probably just seaweed
or something.
- Seaweed in a lake?
- Fine.
It was a lakeweed.
Relax.
(water splashing)
- Did you hear that?
- You're acting a lot like Mia.
Are you sure the
shrooms were okay?
- I just, I don't like this.
Can I go inside, please?
- Babe, just give
me five minutes.
All I need is a rub and a tug.
Fine.
Let's go.
(water splashing)
(ominous music)
(crickets chirping)
- If it's bothering you,
just take it off.
- Yeah.
- Just take it off for a second.
- I think my arm's
just sweaty, babe.
- One second.
It's probably not healthy
to wear those things
24/7 like you do anyways.
- My watch is the only way
I can use my broken phone.
Remember?
- Sorry.
(both laughing)
- Make it up to me.
There's something,
(clearing throat)
there's something I've
been meaning to ask you.
- Oh wait, before you start,
I just wanna say thank
you for this weekend.
Sorry for tripping out earlier.
- No need to apologize.
Do you, you wanna go swimming?
(chuckling) Baby steps.
- No, I'm good but
don't let me stop you.
- You sure?
- How about I sit on the
rocks and watch you swim?
- Hmm.
Okay.
Deal.
(Mia laughing)
(crickets chirping)
(Kai groaning)
- Are you gonna swim
with your watch on?
- It's waterproof.
(water splashing)
(laughing) Babe,
the water's the
perfect temperature.
Ah.
(upbeat dance music)
(water splashing)
- Mom!
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
Kai?
(ominous music)
Kai!
(voice echoing)
Baby?
(bag unzipping)
(phone thudding)
(both moaning)
(hand knocking)
- [Angel] Yeah?
(door clicking)
- Have either of you seen Kai?
- I thought he was out with you.
- He disappeared.
- Are you back
from your trip yet?
- I'm, I'm good.
If either of you see him
can you please let him know
I'm looking for him.
- Kai is always off
exploring something.
This place has so many
little nooks and caves.
He'll be back.
I'm sure.
So yeah.
Do you mind?
I don't wanna lose my momentum
if you know what I mean.
Tick tock, you can fuck off now.
- Fine, fine.
(door clicking)
(both moaning)
- [Angel] I got stamina,
baby, I got stamina.
(Vicki moaning)
(both moaning)
(footsteps thudding)
- What the hell?
(Mia sighing)
(phone chiming)
(door rattling)
(ominous music)
(wind whooshing)
(Mia screaming)
- My apologies.
I didn't mean to startle you.
- Oh no, no, I, I was
actually just looking for you.
- Well, perfect timing.
How can I be of assistance?
Is it the phone?
That thing can be so finicky?
- Oh no, no, no.
Nothing like that.
I seem to have lost track of Kai
and I was wondering if you
might know where he could be.
- You can't find him.
Well, where did
you last see him?
- The lake.
He was swimming.
- Well this land
has lots of history.
I'm sure he is off exploring.
- I told you, he's
off being Kai.
- Maybe he's just
giving you some space.
- Yeah, maybe.
- If I were you,
I would rest my eyes.
I have no doubt
that once you wake,
he'll be right beside you
ready to tell you Of all
the history he's uncovered.
- What sort of places
do people typically
explore this late at night?
- Well, these old lands
have so many nooks
and crannies to get lost in.
I wouldn't go searching for him.
Perhaps something
to help you sleep?
I do have some melatonin
in the cabinets.
- Yeah.
Actually that doesn't
sound too bad.
- Excellent.
Why don't you wash up
and I'll place them
on your nightstand.
(tense music)
(water gurgling)
(Angel coughing)
(water running)
(robe thudding)
(door clicking)
(ominous music)
(Mia gasping)
(ominous music continues)
(door creaking)
(footsteps thudding)
(door clicking)
(ominous music)
(floor creaking)
(ominous music continues)
(intense music)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music)
- Kai, I was looking for you.
- Oh, that's something new.
Normally ladies
run away from me.
- I'm sorry.
I thought you were my boyfriend.
- Well, we can talk later.
Prefer you buy me a drink first.
- You see anyone out here?
- No, miss.
I have not.
Just me.
- [Mia] Okay, thank you.
- Is there something
I can help you with?
- No, sir.
Actually, yeah, my
boyfriend's missing
and I'm starting to
get really worried.
- Oh, I don't know.
He look like a big
dumb kid to me.
He probably just out, just
blowing all over the place.
Nooks and crannies.
- Nooks and crannies
to get lost.
- Yeah, you got the brochure
left on your pillow I see.
- Can you keep an
eye out for him?
- Yes, ma'am.
I surely will.
I'll let you know
if I see anybody.
- Okay.
Thank you, sir.
I, I really appreciate it.
- Not at all.
Mmm, uh huh.
That'll do, pig.
That'll do.
(watch buzzing)
(ominous music)
- God.
(watch buzzing)
What?
(Mia breathing heavily)
Kai?
Wake up.
I think Kai's in trouble.
- I'm sick of this shit.
Mia, you've gotta stop with this
on edge scared school
girl act, okay?
- I think something's
wrong with Kai.
- And we've all
told you, he's fine.
You just refuse to have a
good time wherever we go.
- Babe, that's enough.
- No.
Ever since your parents died,
we've been walking on
eggshells around you.
Kai probably ran
as fast as he could
to get away from
your miserable ass.
- I see how you feel about me,
but I found Kai's watch
and he doesn't go
anywhere without it.
- I said let it go.
If you want to go play
Nancy Drew in the forest,
then he my guest.
But leave me and my woman
out of your little fantasy.
- Is there a problem?
- There is no-
- Yes.
- Look, I heard yelling and I
just wanted to check on you.
- There's something
wrong with Kai.
I found his watch and
he never takes it off.
We have to call the police.
- Are you out of your mind?
- I'm sorry about her.
She's just a little on
edge after all the drugs.
- Excuse me?
- Always, he will.
The authorities around here,
they don't take too kindly
to drugs and psychedelics.
Are you sure you want
to go down that route?
- Yes.
- No.
Some of us care about our future
and don't need any sort of
record fresh out of college.
- Oh, I'm not feeling very well.
- Clearly.
- Babe, why don't you go to bed?
I'll take care of it.
- What was in those
pills that you gave me?
- Completely harmless.
Your standard melatonin.
Just strong enough to
knock a wild toddler out.
- I got you.
(ominous music)
(voice whispering)
- Your aggression.
- Sorry about that.
That girl's just so uptight.
- I liked it.
- Oh?
- I like the big bad
masculine energy.
It's quite intoxicating.
My how you've grown up.
(ominous music continues)
- You have something
on your face.
- Do I?
Show me.
- [Vicki] She's knocked out.
- All right, well goodnight.
- You okay?
You look shook.
- Yeah, I'm fine.
I just need to lay down.
- Aren't you worried
about Kai at all?
- Who?
Mr. Loner?
He'll pop up around here.
(ominous music)
(lid clattering)
(thunder crashing)
- [Kai] Mia.
Mia.
(thunder crashing)
(Mia breathing heavily)
Mia!
(ominous music continues)
- Kai?
(thunder crashing)
(ominous music continues)
- [Kai] Mia!
- Are you...
(rain pattering)
- [Kai] Help me, please.
(thunder crashing)
Help me, Mia!
(Mia breathing heavily)
(bedding rustling)
(latches clicking)
(Mia gasping softly)
(Mia gasping)
(dramatic music)
(dramatic music continues)
(latches clicking)
(door clicking)
(Mia gasping)
(ominous music)
- Vicki, what are
you doing here?
- I was actually
coming to check on you.
- I'm good.
I'm going to look for Kai.
I already know what
you're gonna say,
but I know Kai
and he wouldn't just run off.
Something's wrong and I
intend to figure out what.
- I was actually gonna say,
let me help you.
- Thanks.
I was actually going to the
car to get one of these.
- Great minds think alike.
(keys jingling)
When do you last
remember seeing Kai?
- At the Cove.
- Okay, so we'll start there.
- Good idea.
Thank you, by the way.
It's really nice to
have someone help.
- Well, us girl's gotta
stick together, right?
I'm sorry about Angel earlier.
I've never seen him
get so amped before.
It's like the vibes
of the lake are
doing something to-
- I think you're right.
Something's felt off
since we got here.
- Yeah.
- Let's go.
(crickets chirping)
Let's go this way.
- Okay.
- You got it?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
There.
That's where he
took off his clothes
and jumped in the water.
- I'm sorry but it's kind of
hard to believe that, you know,
he's just gallivanting in
the woods in the middle
of the night with
nothing but swim trunks.
- Exactly.
- Do you remember
hearing anything
or seeing anyone while
you guys were out here?
- No.
No, I was listening to music.
- Are you thinking
what I'm thinking?
- Have you ever
used one of these?
- Does it look like I've
ever used one of those?
- Neither have I, but there's
a first time for everything.
Slow, slow, slow.
- Uh huh.
- Alright, I'm gonna hold the
boat and you're gonna get in.
- Okay.
- Up against the rock
and you're gonna step in.
(tense music)
- Fuck, fuck, fuck.
Okay, we're good.
We're good.
(tense music continues)
- If I remember correctly,
he swam out this way.
- This water gives
me the creeps.
- I thought water was life.
- Yeah.
Beautiful beach water.
Not this murky bullshit.
If you don't mind me asking,
what is your thing
with water anyways.
You know, I can kind
of feel the vibes.
- Um, last year my mom drowned.
I tried to save her but
there was nothing I could do.
- Sick.
I'm sorry about that.
I'm sorry for being such
a jerk to you earlier.
God, you must hate me.
- No, I don't.
It's so odd that
there's no fish,
no, no wildlife.
How many lakes do
you know like that?
- I don't know.
I don't go fishing.
- Oh my god.
(water splashing)
(ominous music)
What sort of animal
could do this?
- Maybe they just fell
off when he was hurrying.
(ominous music continues)
Wait, what are you doing?
- Kai's in the water.
I'm gonna find him.
- If whatever did that to
his shorts is in the water,
you're gonna need like
a weapon or something.
- Don't have time for this.
- Kai's been down
there for hours.
(ominous music continues)
Let's just, let's go back
and help us find
something to search, okay?
And Angel and I
were here earlier.
We saw like an old RV
and there was a bunch
of diving equipment.
I'll go with you.
- Yeah.
Okay.
The water's too dark anyways.
So we'll all go for
something for help.
(water splashing)
(indistinct)
- Just searching.
That's all.
- Are you sure it's over here?
- I'm positive.
- Can't see anything
through this fog.
- It's this way.
Just trust me.
(voice whispering indistinctly)
- Hello?
Vicki?
(voice whispering indistinctly)
- Mia.
- Vicki?
- Oh my God.
- Mia, what happened?
- Where did you go?
- I found the trailer.
I thought you were behind me.
- I'm sorry.
I'm fine, I'm fine.
Let's just go.
Let's go.
- [Vicki] This is it.
- [Mia] How the hell
did you find this place?
- [Vicki] Angel knows this
land like the back of his hand.
Plus we fucked on the
little couch in the RV.
- Of course.
(cans clattering)
(door creaking)
(Mia screaming)
What the hell are
you doing out here?
- I'm the
groundskeeper, remember?
My job is to keep the grounds.
This here my workshop.
I should be asking you
girls that question.
- Her boyfriend went missing.
We were coming for some diving
equipment we saw earlier.
- Oh, you come here looking
for some diver's equipment
that you saw earlier
when you was here
with your lover.
Right?
- You saw us.
- Oh darling, Mr. Mr.
Leonard, he saw everything.
Now this diving equipment
you're talking about,
I hope you're not thinking
of using it to go out on
that lake right now.
I would highly
recommend against it.
There's a lot of
stuff out in that lake
to avoid this time of night.
- What's in the lake?
- Stuff.
Stuff ought not
to be messed with.
Stuff ought stay in the lake.
- I thought everyone said that
there's no wildlife in the
lake or forest around here.
- Oh there isn't.
- Then what stuff
are you referring to?
- Well you see, there's a
lot more things in this world
than just wildlife,
trees, stuff like that.
There's some things
in this world
that just kind of need
their own classification.
Will you hold onto
that, darling?
There you go.
Mmm.
Oh yeah.
There your suit.
- Will you help us?
My boyfriend went swimming
and now he's missing.
- Oh, did he?
Well that sound about
par for the course.
- What does that mean?
I mean stuff like that
tend to happen around here.
Like some kind of
unavoidable thing
that is, well, unavoidable.
- What's in the
lake, Mr. Leonard?
- Like I said, stuff.
However, if you two have
taken it into your head
that you absolutely
gotta go play crabby ass
out there at this hour,
well, you are going to
need a little bit more
than that flashlight,
Nancy Drew.
That little bitty thing.
- Hell no.
I did not sign up for
no "Hunger Games" shit.
- I like her.
She got her head
screwed on right.
- With you or not,
I'm gonna go find Kai.
- Oh you ain't gonna find him?
Mm-mm.
See, folks that go
missing out in no water.
You can take it, I don't bite.
They seldom come back.
- I intend to be the
exception to the rule.
- Oh, I know what you intend.
You let me know how
that work out for you.
You just gotta jiggle
the little red thing.
It'll open up, you'll find it.
Watch your step on the way out.
Please close it on your way out.
Watch your step.
I get it.
I'm used to that.
- Mia.
Mia, slow down.
For Christ sake, I'm in heels.
Mia, just because I don't
wanna go in the water
does not mean I don't
wanna help you find Kai.
- The lake is the
only lead we have.
- Well maybe I could just
take the car and drive around.
- Drive around where?
There's only forest around here.
- I don't know.
When Angel and I
came up earlier,
there were so many dirt roads.
Maybe, just maybe Kai's
at a nearby property.
- You and Angel sure did
notice a lot when you came in.
- Well we kind of had
some time to kill.
- You should check out
the nearby properties
and I'll check out the lake.
- Okay.
Meet back at the car in 30?
- Vicki?
- Yeah.
Thanks again.
- It's nothing.
Us girls gotta stick together.
Right?
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
- [Angel] Going somewhere?
- It's Mia.
She's still looking for Kai.
I figured take the car and go.
- [Angel] You know
as well as I do
that there's nothing down those
roads for at least 10 miles.
- I know, but peace of mind.
(Angel sighing)
- Before you go, get me right.
- Babe, now's not the time.
- Are you serious?
Get out.
- Babe.
- I said get out.
(door slamming)
- Jesus.
Can I help you?
- I got a message the
shower wasn't working.
- It was working just
fine for me earlier.
Maybe it's Angel.
He's in there asleep,
but you can check it out.
- Well if this is a bad
time, I can come by later.
- Well how long
is it gonna take?
- Well that old thing just
needs a good hand, right?
- Well you can go in,
just don't wake him.
He's in a grumpy mood.
- I'll be quiet as a mouse.
Going somewhere?
- Yeah.
I just wanna clear my head.
- Understood.
Some advice from a native.
- Sure.
What?
- Make your first right.
You'll see the most
perfect view of the lake.
- Thanks.
(door clicking)
(crickets chirping)
(boat rattling)
(water splashing)
(oar thudding)
(Mia gasping)
(ominous music)
(brush rustling)
(ominous music continues)
(voices whispering indistinctly)
- Kai?
(crickets chirping)
(oar thudding)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
(water splashing)
(water gurgling)
(crickets chirping)
(water splashing)
(Mia gasping)
(ominous music)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music continues)
(water splashing)
Oh God!
(ominous music continues)
(water splashing)
(Mia screaming)
(creature croaking)
(ominous music)
(water splashing)
(Mia gasping)
(Mia screaming)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music continues)
(Mia gasping)
(Mia groaning)
Okay, okay. (breathing heavily)
(Mia gasping)
(engine revving)
- It's a bout time with
all these side quests.
Back from your
little goose chase?
(metal creaking)
(ominous music)
Oh, sorry, I thought
you were Vicki.
- I told Victoria my
shower wasn't working.
She said it was all
right if I used yours.
She said you wouldn't mind.
- Really?
Did she?
- She said you were
sleeping and to be careful
because you can get
frisky when you wake.
- Yeah, I'm feeling
frisky indeed.
- Would you mind helping me
reach those hard
to reach places?
- With what should I reach?
- [Sabrina] Give me your hand.
- I can do a whole
lot more than that.
(ominous music)
(water running)
(both breathing heavily)
(Angel gagging)
(ominous music continues)
(Mia screaming)
- Mr...
Mr. Leonard?
(ominous music continues)
(door slamming)
(cans clattering)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music continues)
(door slamming)
(door clicking)
(floor creaking)
(phone ringing and buzzing)
(Mia gasping)
(door clicking)
(phone ringing and buzzing)
(Mia grunting)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(footsteps thudding)
- What are you doing in my room?
What's that?
- What is Kai's phone
doing in your bag?
- That's not Kai's phone.
- What is Kai's phone
doing in your bag?
- Look, I know what
this looks like,
but you're gonna
have to trust me.
- Answer the question, Vicki.
- There's something
else going on here.
- What is his phone
doing in your bag?
- I don't know.
I don't know how his
phone ended up in my bag.
Okay?
- Where is the car?
- That's what I came
back to explain.
- You took the only
working car to go search
for Kai and now that's gone.
- That woman, Sabrina, she
told me where I might be able
to find him and the
road she sent me down,
there was some sharp in there.
I don't know, the
tires just burst.
I had to walk back.
- That's convenient.
Now we're trapped here with
no car and no cell service.
- I'm telling you,
it's the old hag.
She was lurking in my
room right before I left.
- Why would she put his phone
at the bottom of your bag?
- Because of this
moment right here.
Mia, she wants to divide us up.
- Where is Angel?
- I don't know.
But we can look for
Angel and Kai together.
We can not split up.
We have to stick together, Mia.
- Yeah, yeah, you're right.
We can use the kitchen
line to call for help.
- Okay, that sounds good.
(Vicki sighing)
(vase shattering)
(ominous music)
(Mia whimpering)
- I'm sorry but I have
to do this on my own.
(ominous music continues)
(phone beeping)
- [Operator] Emergency services.
How may I help you?
- Yes, my boyfriend, friends,
and I at the Lake Pearl Inn.
My boyfriend's missing-
- Emergency services.
How may I help you?
Emergency services.
- Yes.
Can you hear me?
Hello?
- You will all die tonight.
- What the fuck?
(door creaking)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music continues)
(box clacking)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music continues)
(footsteps thudding)
(Mia gasping)
- Mia?
Are you in here?
(ominous music)
(vase shattering)
(Vicki shouting)
- Oh you fucking- (gasping)
(ominous music)
(Vicki groaning)
(Sabrina grunting)
(ominous music continues)
(both grunting)
where's Angel?
(ominous music continues)
(both grunting)
(Vicki coughing)
(Vicki grunting)
Where's angel,
you fucking bitch?
(knife stabbing)
(ominous music continues)
(Vicki groaning)
- So bold.
(knife stabbing)
(ominous music continues)
So you thought
you could best me?
(ominous music continues)
(Mia gasping)
- Vicki.
It's okay.
Stop.
Stay with me, please.
Please stay with me, please.
Just keep breathing.
It's okay, it's okay.
(Vicki gagging)
I'm so sorry.
Oh my God. (sobbing)
(door creaking)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(Mia gasping)
(dramatic music)
(footsteps thudding)
(crickets chirping)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(Mia grunting)
(Mia gasping)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(crickets chirping)
(liquid sloshing)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(crickets chirping)
(ominous music)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(ominous music continues)
(liquid sloshing)
(Mr. Leonard coughing)
One move, one sound and I
will jam this up your throat.
- All right.
- Now tell me what the fuck
is going on around here.
- Well, since you
asked so nicely,
but not here, this
lake out here.
Won't mind if we go to my place?
- Lead the way.
- Just up the hill there.
(dramatic music)
You know, you don't
gotta use that.
I'm on your side.
- Didn't seem that way.
What were you
dumping in the lake?
- Well now that a long story
I can't make short.
I'm over here.
- [Mia] Don't try
anything funny.
- [Mr. Leonard] Why
would I do that?
Like I told you,
I'm on your side.
- [Mia] And which side's that?
- [Mr. Leonard] The only side.
(door clicking)
(cans clattering)
- Tell me what the
hell is going on.
- Yeah, let me just,
nah, (coughing) I guess
there really ain't
much point taking these no more.
(coughing) Why don't you
have a sit down there.
I think we got a little bit
of time before the next phase.
(Mr. Leonard sighing)
I'll just light
a cigarette here.
- Enough games.
- Ha.
Don't do me any favors.
You won't hit me right now,
but you pull that trigger,
I guarantee y'all be dead
before the sun come up.
I'm no mathematician,
but I figure if you listen
to me, you got about a,
I don't know, 10% chance of
living through the night.
Yeah, you're a smart girl.
Listen, my family,
we've been caretakers
at Lake Pearl Inn
property for generations.
It is part of our duty
that I call it in.
It's a, it's a family curse.
We gotta work for the goon.
- The goon?
The water goddess legend
you were telling us about?
- Water goddess.
She a monster.
- I know you told us
the legend earlier.
- Now the story is true,
all of it, but there is a piece
of important information I
always leave out when I tell it.
- And what's that?
- All them years ago
when all them men
had their back
against that water,
that going be right here
on this piece of land.
The goon didn't exist.
She was just a, a water spirit.
You know, kind of a source
of energy and whatnot.
It took the sacrifice
of 100, 150 men
to get her to walk up out
that water in corporeal form.
You hear?
- That's a cute story, but
how does that help me here?
- I am getting to it.
I just need to catch my breath.
The point is
(lighter clicking)
that without the sacrifice,
there is no goon.
You see?
So years ago the local news,
some of you internet
watchdog influencers,
they kinda got wind of what
was happening down here,
left us some pretty
bad reviews on Yelp.
Anyway, kind of shut our
operation down for a bit.
She ain't had a sacrifice
in over 15 years.
If she don't get a
sacrifice tonight,
she'll return to her
water form forever.
- I assure you, I
have no intention
of sacrificing myself
to that fish bitch.
- She don't care about
your skinny ass, girl.
But your boyfriend, (coughing)
he not going be so lucky.
- Kai would never.
- "Kai would never."
Nobody ever would.
But extreme torture,
that make people
do crazy things.
- Human torture.
- She got away
with getting men down
the edge of that water.
- And why would she spare you?
- Were you not listening to
the whole family curse thing
two minutes ago? (coughing)
My ancestor, great-great
grandfather, whatever,
he was that last man alive
when she come up out the water,
and he was the first one
to go down to his knee
and bow to her, bow to the goon.
Goddesses being what they are,
she kind of dug that.
She let him live,
but he got the bow.
From then on him and
all his descendants,
they work for her now.
So all these generations,
we have been doing her
dirty work for her.
Pulling the grass,
inviting the guests,
burying the bodies.
That all stops tonight with me.
(lighter clicking)
Many years ago, I made
sure there wouldn't be
anymore Mr. Leonards.
(clippers snipping)
That bloodline's done.
Meet here tonight.
What I need to know from you...
(Mr. Leonard groaning)
My father, he read up some
things about the goon.
Apparently this is the only
thing that can kill her,
but I gotta get her when she
in the water in goddess form.
See?
So what I need from you,
you just gotta keep her
preoccupied for a minute
or two till I can get
this all up in her.
All right?
- How?
(footsteps thudding)
- You need to hide right quick.
She coming.
I have room back there.
(cans clattering)
(tense music)
(lighter clicking)
- Leonard.
- (coughing) Yes ma'am.
- Did you harvest the eggs?
- Of course I did.
When am I not?
- Good.
(lighter clicking)
- Shall be ready to
hatch next season?
- Yes, they will be.
(lighter clicking)
- Seems you've had company.
- Yeah, them brats.
They've been stalking
around here since
they showed up.
- I've since made
waste of one girl.
- I hardly think that other
one gonna be much of a match-
- You dare suggest otherwise.
- No ma'am.
I apologize.
I didn't mean any
disrespect by that.
How can I help you, goddess?
(cans clattering)
- You live in fifth.
- I apologize.
My fault. (coughing)
Oh, I apologize.
That's pretty nasty.
I'm sorry you had to see that.
(dramatic music)
- It appears I shall need a
new groundskeeper very soon.
- Yeah, pretty likely.
How about one, one
of the boys up there?
You think they'd be a
suitable replacement?
- I haven't had the
ritual in many years.
- Yeah, that local news,
they did a job on us.
That's for sure.
- I can't afford to lose
another sacrificial soul.
My earthly powers are waining.
Two men should sustain my powers
for getting longer.
- Yes.
- This would do nicely.
(can clattering)
(cans clattering)
(Mr. Leonard coughing)
I shall see you at
the lake before dawn.
- As you wish, goddess.
(door clicking)
(door slamming)
(ominous music)
You need to get
out of here quick.
We don't got much time.
- Where is he?
- He's in the garage.
- The garage?
I checked in there.
He's been in there
this whole time?
- Got a secret room in
the back to the left
you walk in.
Remember, (coughing)
I just need a couple minutes
you keeping her busy.
I take care of the rest.
Now go on, get outta here.
And please remember
to shut the...
Oh fuck my life. (coughing)
(ominous music)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(door clicking)
(ominous music continues)
(no audio)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(objects clattering)
(wall banging)
(Kai screaming and grunting)
(dramatic music)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(metal clacking)
(ominous music)
(ominous music continues)
- Kai?
Oh.
Baby, please wake up.
Please wake up.
Oh, you're okay.
It's okay.
- Where's Vicki?
(Mia sobbing)
I have your watch.
(ominous music)
(Sabrina grunting)
- Two is company.
Three, three is a crowd.
I debated heavily whether
or not to outright kill you.
I surmise that you have
a very strong will,
and a strong will makes
for a great sacrifice.
(electricity crackling)
(Mia grunting)
(Mia groaning)
This one loves you
as only a fool would.
He's been crying
"Mia" all night.
(Mia screaming)
(electricity crackling)
Why are you doing this to us?
Stop.
(electricity crackling)
(Mia screaming)
- I suppose we have time.
Sacrifice is an important tool.
The balance.
For without it, we are merely
immortal energy sources.
Each sacrifice
makes you stronger
and more than just energy.
This holds the power
of the first tribute
the tribes of Pearl gifted me.
- Tribes?
- They were the kind folks
who lived in this land.
I was their water goddess.
They kept their lakes
clean and full of fish.
I appeared to them
as a beam of light
or a kiss of wind
on their cheek.
- I know the story.
The war.
- Their war drove
out all the wildlife.
It poisoned the land.
Like you said, nature
always gets her revenge.
That sacrifice,
those souls bound
to the mortal were,
and goddess in the
physical realm,
is a mortal being.
And that sacrifice
granted me power
that lasted hundreds of years.
But as the years went
on, the days of old faded
and the sacrifices stopped.
Mortality weakens.
So I had to get a little
bit more creative.
(Kai groaning)
- Stop!
(electricity crackling)
Stop, you crazy bitch!
- I've tried,
unsuccessfully, of course,
to sustain my power
in other ways,
but what can not be
cured must be endured.
And this is the only way.
- How is any of this
gonna make us sacrifice
our lives to you?
- Sacrifice is born
out of love or fear.
(electricity crackling)
And if I cannot
make you love me,
I will make you fear me,
and I will torture you
till you choose death.
- We'll never choose death.
(electricity crackling)
No!
(Angel gasping)
(ominous music)
- I'll do it.
- No.
- You should have
spoken for yourself.
- Angel, don't, please.
I'll get us outta here.
I promise.
- Your will is admirable.
Your soul will
taste the sweetest.
Say it again.
- Please, just kill me.
- Well, you have to kill
yourself for it to work.
Do you vow to do it in my name?
(electricity crackling)
(Angel groaning)
- Yes, anything.
I'll do it.
Just please make it stop.
- Perfection.
- Angel, don't give your life
to this crazy bitch!
(electricity crackling)
(ominous music)
(fire crackling)
(crickets chirping)
(Mia grunting)
(ominous music)
(water splashing)
- It's time.
The night is rich and thick.
(ominous music continues)
Leonard, bring me the serum.
- [Mr. Leonard] Yes, ma'am.
Here, you're gonna
need this too.
(ominous music continues)
(Sabrina gasping)
(Sabrina breathing heavily)
- [Sabrina] Are you ready?
- Yes.
- No, Angel, stop.
- Silence her, Leonard.
- Gladly, Mrs.
(ominous music continues)
(punch thudding)
- Hello again.
Hello, lady.
You well enough to
finish this job?
I got one left.
There's a knife behind
that white rock,
behind this over here.
You gonna have to stab her
while she in water form.
All right?
I'm done.
(dramatic music)
(chains clacking)
- Now repeat after me.
I, Angel Parrish-
- I, Angel Parrish-
- [Sabrina] Sacrifice myself-
- Sacrifice myself-
- To the water goddess.
(chains clanking)
- Sacrifice myself
to the water goddess.
- Now walk into the lake.
(Angel sobbing)
(dramatic music continues)
- Stop.
(water splashing)
(ominous music)
(voices whispering)
- I can feel his life
force leave his body
and join mine.
(Mr. Leonard coughing)
- That can't be good. (groaning)
Absolutely.
(lighter clicking)
I should have picked
one up at the 7-Eleven.
(voice whispering)
(Sabrina gasping)
- You're next.
- Mia.
Mia.
- Mia is gone.
(punch thudding)
And it's not about her.
It's about me.
- Mrs., please,
we gotta sacrifice
we need to get going.
- Oh yes.
Now repeat after me.
I, Kai Oats-
- I, Kai Oats-
- Sacrifice myself-
Say it or I'll kill you slowly.
(Sabrina gasping)
(dramatic music)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(dramatic music continues)
Silly mortal.
(knife thudding)
(Mia grunting)
As delicious as your
sacrifice would've been,
it appears I need a
new groundskeeper.
You and your future generations
will serve my will
until the end of time.
- [Mia] I will never
allow that to happen.
- Once I have my
final sacrifice, it
won't be your choice.
(Mia grunting)
(ominous music)
(Mia groaning)
(Mia gasping)
(bone snapping)
(Mia screaming)
(hand thudding)
(ominous music continues)
Fool until the end.
- [Mia] Hey!
(ominous music)
(Mia gasping)
(ominous music continues)
(Mia breathing heavily)
- Now where were we?
Oh, yes, that's right.
You were about to kill yourself
in tribute to me.
Now repeat after me.
I, Kai Oats-
- I, Kai Oats-
- Sacrifice myself-
- To the water goddess.
- Now walk into the lake.
(ominous music continues)
(chains clacking)
(voices whispering)
(Sabrina groaning)
(ominous music continues)
- No, please stop.
Please.
(voices whispering)
(ominous music continues)
(chains clacking)
(water splashing)
(ominous music continues)
(Mia screaming)
(water splashing)
(Sabrina screaming)
(Mia gasping)
(ominous music continues)
(Mia breathing heavily)
(Mia whimpering)
Please wake up.
Please.
(ominous music continues)
(water splashing)
- Well, that there gonna
leave a mark, that is.
(Kai coughing)
- It's okay, it's
okay, it's okay.
It's okay, it's okay.
(Kai coughing)
I thought I lost you.
(Kai breathing heavily)
(Mia sobbing)
(dramatic music)
(Kai breathing heavily)
- Angel, Vicki?
- No.
I'm so sorry.
(Kai sobbing)
I know. (sobbing)
- [Kai] I love you so much.
(dramatic music continues)
I wanted to ask you
something all week.
- I know.
I know, I know.
Yes.
(dramatic music continues)
(water splashing)
♪ My heartbeat cuts right
through the silence ♪
♪ I breathe peace
within the violence ♪
♪ Every time I speak ♪
♪ Gives me a chance to
see with my eyes closed ♪
♪ Find my way home ♪
♪ Find the light
within the darkness ♪
♪ Cut the rope that
ties the hardest ♪
♪ Doesn't matter
where you've been ♪
♪ What only matters is
where you're going ♪
♪ So go ahead and go there ♪
♪ Yeah, yeah ♪
♪ I am, I am, I am, I am ♪
♪ Help me ride
into the darkness ♪
♪ My cheeks are damped ♪
♪ Your eyes are running ♪
♪ Every time I speak ♪
♪ Gives me a chance to
see with my eyes closed ♪
♪ Find my way home ♪
♪ Find the light
within the darkness ♪
♪ Cut the rope that
ties behind us ♪
♪ Doesn't matter
where you've been ♪
♪ Only matters
where you're going ♪
♪ Go ahead and go there ♪
(dramatic percussive
music continues)